(Sheldon:)Besides disrupting the local gravity field.
(Leonard:)If he were any bigger,
he'd have moons orbiting him.
- Oh, snap.
- Ha-ha.
(Sheldon:)So I guess we'll be leaving now.
(Leonard:)Why should we leave?
(Leonard:)For all we know, he crashed the party
and Penny doesn't even want him here.
You have a backup hypothesis?
Maybe they just wanna be friends.
(Sheldon:)Or maybe she wants to be friends
and he wants something more.
(Leonard:)Then he and I are on equal ground.
(Sheldon:)Yes, but you're much closer to it
than he is.
(Leonard:)Look, if this was 15,000 years ago,
by virtue of his size and strength...
(Leonard:)...Kurt would be entitled
to his choice of female partners.
(Sheldon:)And male partners, animal partners,
large primordial eggplants...
(Sheldon:)...pretty much
whatever tickled his fancy.
(Leonard:)Yes, but our society
has undergone a paradigm shift.
(Leonard:)In the information age, Sheldon,
you and I are the alpha males.
- And we shouldn't have to back down.
- True.